All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Gold Roger and his crew were the only men to ever chart these waters and learn all the secrets they held.
For the rest of the pirates of the world, this has proven to be the end of the road, a graveyard of dreams.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I will be the king of the pirates!
It's been two years since the War of the Best in Marineford.
Scattered across the world, Luffy and his crew underwent special training to prepare for the trials ahead.
Now, thousands of feet below sea level, they set sail to the next step of their journey, Fishman Island.
My turn!
Gum gum!
Elephant guide!
Hey, that's Naughty!
You know better, Uncle Ho!
You're not allowed to eat ships!
Wait, did he just help us?
Who freaking cares?
Let's just make a break for it!
He might change his mind!
Gah!
Oh, please no more!
Undersea Volcanic Eruption!
Drifting to the Fishman Island!
Dead men tell no tales, and dead men have no...
Is he...
Seth?
Me?
I pluck the rings right off their hands within these shadowy seas.
Dead men have no regrets and no tears left to weep.
I'll pluck the crowns right off their heads within this cold, black deep.
Sunken treasures free for the taking!
A king of pirates in the making!
I leave my enemies weeping and shaking!
Van der Decken is my name!
And these long-lost riches I do claim!
Go away!
No, it can't be!
It's a ghost ship!
You are the last one who should be scared!
Boy, you can't get with these moves!
Whoa!
No!
It's a ghost ship!
Tell us that thing isn't real!
Tell us it's like your ship!
Nothing would make me happier, but take a look at their sail...
That's the legendary Flying Dutchman!
It shouldn't be here!
It shouldn't exist!
As the story goes, it sailed the seas hundreds of years ago.
One dark and stormy night,
the captain of the ship suddenly lost his mind.
Consumed with madness, he threw his own crewmates
into the sea one after another.
Then he turned his gaze to the heavens
and cursed the very gods.
The captain's name was none other than Vander Decken,
and the ship was the Flying Dutchman.
The gods condemned him for his actions,
and he was cursed for all eternity.
Sailing the seas aimlessly, there on that very vessel.
Even if you're a skeleton who has sailed on a ghost ship of your own,
the sight of the Flying Dutchman will put chills down your spine.
Stop screaming.
We thought Brooks' ship was scary when we saw it.
Look how that turned out.
There was a logical explanation.
Sure, if someone Brooks' jokes are so bad, you could scream,
but that's the worst of it.
You're so cold!
Almost like you're made of metal!
Get it?
Frankie's right.
The ship may look spooky,
but that doesn't mean the scary story is real.
Perhaps.
But the Kraken is a legend as well,
and it just attacked our ship.
This is all uncharted territory for us.
I mean, who's to say what's real and what's not?
If Robin says it's real...
Then it's gotta be!
We're doomed!
Someone hold it!
Robin, don't torment the crew just so you can have a laugh.
We're in real trouble here.
Good news, Captain Vanderdekken!
Waratsumi and Ankara are bringing in the pirate ship!
Foolish humans, all of them.
But the ship does look rather nice.
And their treasure will look even nicer once it's in my hands!
Bye!
You pay!
Please!
Yeah!
Sorry, I'm touching you!
You got me?
Me?
What, are my giant muscles not good enough to protect you?
Either way, we gotta pull it together so we're still alive when they do come back!
It's getting hotter and hotter.
That's not normal.
That can only mean...
Listen up.
I'm not digging their treasure out of your stomachs, so no eating the ship.
Let's give it a good knock.
Huh?
You betcha!
I think we're about to get pounded!
Well, sure!
He's our enemy!
Frankie, we need a coup to burst, now!
I can't!
We used up all our fuel already!
That means we're on our own till I can restock the cola supply!
Do something!
We're dead!
Oh, oh!
Oh!
Whoa! You big boy!
Alright! He learned his lesson!
Enough!
Good boy!
Huh?
Hey!
Guys! I thought you were dead!
That was so scary!
What the heck happened to you?
Mummy swan! Robin!
It was crazy, that's for sure!
They got lost. Morons.
They're hopeless without me.
Sanji, no! He's having a girl-crazy relapse!
We'll have to build up his tolerance with some less stimulating pictures!
You gonna take that, Guarazumi?
Get back up! Avenge yourself! Start swinging!
My bubble popped and suited Sanji's, so we all had to crowd inside Zoro's before he drowned!
We were running out of air!
How about you stop scaring us like that?
Now, a song for you, Captain.
Finally! I can stretch my legs!
Lucy! We thought you were gone forever!
You survived that! You can survive anything!
No kidding! And you tamed the Kraken, just like you said!
I thought you were nuts!
So, is he going to be our new guide?
Yeah! If that goopy dude can have a sea monster pull his ship, then we can have Sudame pull the Sunny! Right, pal?
Of course you would name it already, wouldn't you?
The Captain's insane to give us such a name, but as long as it can cover us, I won't complain!
Now, pull the Sunny forward! Let's go!
Uh, that's cool if he wants to give us a free ride.
But make sure he doesn't crush us with those giant tentacles!
Captain! The ship's getting away!
You think I can't see the Kraken? Follow them!
What's that?
Captain, stop! We gotta turn back or we're dead!
I knew it! An undersea volcano! Straight ahead!
What?!
Looks like it's about to blow!
Pull back, men!
We'll live to plunder another day!
Roger! You don't gotta ask me twice!
Antelope! Maratsumi! Draw the ship!
Okay, Gaston, sure!
And the Tekken is my name, and these long-loss bridges, I'll delay her!
Yeah!
Oh, no!
Luffy, I don't know how the Kraken works, but order him to turn around and haul ass!
Hey, Sotomi!
Wait a sec!
He's hauling ass just fine all on his own!
We're such a giant monster, it's kind of shameful, actually!
Who cares? I would be doing the same thing!
He runs terribly!
Give him a break! I'd rather be clumsy and alive than graceful and dead!
Like me?
What the hell is Mouthbrow doing?
Woo!
Yeah!
Baby!
It's rehab!
Come on! I wanna see lava!
Evacuate to the front of the ship!
Hurry!
That's not gonna help! It's just a couple of feet!
Woo!
Well, you've got your lava, Luffy.
It's getting hotter.
Nobody told me we could be boiled alive down here!
The ocean sure hates us!
Woo!
Woo! Woo!
Hey!
Come on!
knew you!
Thday Souroume!
Somebody is going to be eating your delicious cooked carcass from off the ocean floor!
Ooh, riding him is pretty fun, but eating him might be even better!
The temperature change! It's causing a vortex in the current!
Nami, which direction is Fishman Island? We can't lose our way to...
We're not ready for real world yet, Santi! Go back to your pictures and relax!
Straight ahead! I have an idea!
We're getting closer!
Now, jump into the trench!
That doesn't look safe!
That's not a place you jump! It's an abyss!
Yeah, there's something for blackness down there!
Fish people live there! They've got to be insane!
Lava! There's lava behind us!
And the void in front of us! Help!
Can't we go up? Up where's that burning and dark and everything wants to kill us?
Wait! You're not really loony, are you? You're some evil demon who looks like him who wants to drag us to the depths of hell!
This is a nightmare! Why can't I wake up?
Zootaman! Jump in!
Yes!
It's erupting again!
Whoa! Look above us! Something's coming down!
Baldur's? A mudslide?
A mudslide?
It's an avalanche! Brace yourself!
The eruption knocked the rocks loose!
If one of those hits us, then the sun is done for!
Our bubble would burst even if we weren't crushed to death!
Dodge the boulders, Tsurume!
I can't just sit here! I'm gonna go cut them!
Luffy, hold onto my leg, okay?
Sure! Gotcha!
Zara, you can't!
What's the big idea?
Yeah, let him go!
Robin!
The ship is over 8,000 meters deep right now!
Never mind the boulders!
Go outside or the water pressure will crush you!
Fine, but we gotta do something!
We don't have to destroy anything!
We just need to buy some time to get away from the cliff wall!
Leave it to me, then!
Special Attack Green Star Sargasso!
Go!
Ya!
Oh!
Usa made seaweed appear!
It stopped the boulders!
That's handy!
Oh, wow!
Nice shot!
No, Uncle!
It won't hold for very long, though!
We gotta get moving, Tsurume!
Move it!
Just in time!
Yeah!
Monster plants!
Monster plants?
Oh, man!
That's cool!
I wonder what else you have in there!
That big bag of creatures!
This is not mine and it'll surprise me!
No, Uncle!
It won't hold for very long, though!
We gotta get moving, Tsurume!
Move it!
Just in time!
Monster plants?
Oh man, that's cool!
I wonder what else you have in that big bag of tricks.
Looks like we're in the clear!
I trained my butt off, you know.
Actually, yeah, here!
I'll tell you!
It's a very touching story, I promise!
The food!
The forbidden temptation!
A cruel diet my master put me through!
Okay, rude!
That Nami, so harsh!
You were pretty great too, Tsurume!
Thanks a bunch!
Yeah, you saved us all!
You're the best, Tsurume!
Tsurume!
Ah!
Oh!
Aren't we alive? Or dead?
There's light. But we're so deep in the sea.
So bright. I've got stars in my eyes.
Rather, just stars. There aren't any eyes.
Guys! Check it out! Over there!
I think we made it!
I can't see anything. It's too bright.
Come on, Nami! Tell us!
Yep. There's no doubt about it.
The needle is pointing straight ahead.
We did it!
Fishman Island!
It's huge!
It's in a giant bubble.
It looks like they have clouds.
There must be air inside.
Whoa! Does that mean we're 10,000 meters deep now?
It's not as scary as I thought.
The trees really do reach all the way to the bottom.
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
All right!
We made it!
The new world is next!
Almost there!
Well, what do you know?
The moron survived after all.
This is where the mermaids live.
Real life, beautiful mermaids!
My dream can finally come true!
Hell, I've longed to see their faces,
to touch them!
A mermaid for me!
A mermaid for you!
A mermaid for...
Stop!
You're not ready for this!
You shouldn't even think about it!
I'm sorry!
I thought my treatment would do the trick!
I know it's your dream,
but you're not healthy enough for mermaids!
Doctor!
For him, this is a fate worse than death!
There's gotta be something you can do!
If he sees mermaids, it will be death!
How cruel!
I don't care...
Sanji!
I don't want to live in a world without dreams.
I'd rather die leering in some hot mermaid tail.
You're the worst!
Who needs blood?
I have lust to sustain me!
Whoa!
It's let your rebirth bright!
I'm so hungry!
I bet they fry up all kinds of yummy deep-sea monsters down here!
Hey!
Wipe up that drool and tell Soda Mae to go!
There's an entrance around here somewhere,
and we've gotta find it!
Guys!
We got company!
Oh, crap.
That's not good.
Sea monsters!
Giant ones!
And now we're dead!
Wow, they look tough!
I want one!
Wait, is somebody riding them?
Yeah!
Although Fishman Island is at sight,
Luffy's descent is halted by a crew of fishmen
riding atop massive sea monsters.
Calling themselves the new Fishman Pirates,
they speak of Luffy's old adversary, Arlong.
Running out of time,
the Straw Hats attempt a desperate maneuver
to propel themselves straight into their destination
at any cost.
On the next One Piece,
landing at the Fishman Island,
beautiful mermaids,
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!